Miss Tsuda!
Thanks for stepping in the other day.
Your support kept the project on track.
I'm really sorry for all the trouble I caused you!
Miss Ito,
we're on the same team.
Of course I've got your back.
If anything,
I'd rather hear a simple "thank you."
Tsuda!
Coming!
Thank you so much! Thank you! Thank...
Do you have a moment
to discuss tomorrow's presentation?
Sure thing.
So, as for features we can add to the language area...
I work for a major electronics manufacturer,
in the planning department for AI household robots,
which keeps me busy every day.
All right, that's it for me for today.
What's so great about virtual reality?
Sure, the section lead said
that AI wasn't going to take my job.
But he can't know that for sure!
What if I do lose my job to a hot new AI
and wind up unemployed?
I might die alone in this filthy pit.
I'll hire myself a pretty little maid!
All-purpose maid robot? Nope! Maid cafe? Nope!
Wow, they left something this big unattended?
Oof, this is heavy!
Wait, I should've opened the door first! Darn it!
Master?
Master, it's time to wake up.
Good morning, Master.
Did you sleep well last night?
Who are you? Where'd you come from?
From the cardboard box in the doorway.
That enormous box!
Did I buy an actual human girl?!
Not at all.
Look, my charging port is on the back of my neck.
I am a gynoid designed for sexual use.
My name is Nadeshiko.
That sounds shady! This has to be illegal!
I'm gonna get arrested, sentenced, and fired...
Now, now.
First, just touch me as I give you the user tutorial.
They're so soft.
I was built with the "idealized human form" in mind,
equipped with finely tuned pressure sensors
that respond to even the faintest stimula—
You felt that?
Yes.
Not even my company
has humanoid robots this elaborate.
Master?
Where did that come from?!
You were staring at my lips,
so I thought you wanted a kiss.
I was just thinking!
Was it unsatisfactory?
I am certain that my oral cavity's specs are fine, so...
How about my genitalia?
That's downright incredible.
If you insert your finger,
I can officially register you as my master.
I'm not sure about that.
I see. Then you're a bottom, Master.
Don't take everything I say as horny!
Understood.
We can conduct the registration another time.
Lastly, we'll perform
a direct demonstration of my body.
Relax and leave everything to me.
Wait! Where are you putting that finger?!
Do not worry.
I assure you I'll guide you to ecstasy.
My tongue and fingertips have multiple sensors
capable of detecting your erogenous zones.
Ah, there's one.
Also, I compile detailed
reports during sexual activity,
so that the quality of our sexual
experience will improve with each session.
So does that mean
this girl is going to have a record
of all my most embarrassing spots?!
I just activated my finger's vibrate function.
By smoothly modulating the strength
and direction of the vibration,
I've never done this before,
we can maximize your pleasure.
but it feels so good!
I can't stop! Oh no...
It's a good thing you had the day off from work.
Thanks to that,
I was able to tend to you all day long, Master.
I think my life might be over.